<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mess</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="tea">The simple elixir of tea is of our natural world. The
        tea leaf is a product of the Earth\'s fertile soil, radiant sun and
        nurturing rain. The water in which it is steeped is one of the Earth\'s
        primary and most powerful elements. Together they make an incredible
        beverage of life to savor and dwell in.in the mess it is served as
        white tea or black tea</string>
    <string name="bread">Bread is a staple food prepared from a dough of flour and
        water, usually by baking. Throughout recorded history it has been a
        prominent food in large parts of the world and is one of the oldest
        man-made foods, having been of significant importance since the dawn
        of agriculture. in the mess they are served in 4 slices and one can
        choose to take with margarine or not </string>
    <string name="potatoes"> fried potatoes are made by first Peeling the
        potatoes as desired. Slice into1/4-inch-thick slices or cut into 3/4-inch
        chunks. In a large skillet
        over medium heat, melt about 2 teaspoons butter or margarine
        per medium potato. Add cooked potatoes; cook about 10 minutes or
        until golden brown, turning occasionally.</string>
    <string name="mahamri">mahamri is a very popular delicacy enjoyed in
        tanzania and other countries nearby, and goes well with tea or
        coffee. The basic ingredients are simple, mixing flour, sugar and eggs.</string>
    <string name="bajia">this is a popular street food which is easy to make by frying
        a batter consisting of simple ingredients such as Black eyed peas, Coriander,
        Onion, Salt, curry powder. It is enjoyed hot with chutney or hot sauce.</string>
    <string name="sausage">A sausage is a cylindrical meat product usually made
        from ground meat, often pork, beef, or veal, along with salt, spices and
        other flavourings, and breadcrumbs, encased by a skin. Typically,
        a sausage is formed in a casing traditionally made from intestine,
        but sometimes from synthetic materials. Sausages that are sold raw are
        cooked in many ways, including pan-frying, broiling and barbecuing.
        Some sausages are cooked during processing and the casing may then be removed. </string>
    <string name="ugali">Ugali is a type of cornmeal porridge made in Africa.It is
        also known as nshima, pap, phutu, sadza, and other names. It is sometimes
        made from other flours, such as millet or sorghum flour, and is sometimes
        mixed with cassava flour. It is cooked in boiling water or milk until it
        reaches a stiff or firm dough-like consistency.</string>
    <string name="rice">Rice is the seed of the grass species Oryza sativa or Oryza
        glaberrima. As a cereal grain, it is the most widely consumed staple food
        for a large part of the world\'s human population. it is prepared by Pouring the
        rice into a pan over a low heat, then add the butter or oil, if using, and
        stir to coat the rice grains. Add double the amount of
        water (2 cups, or 150ml water for a 75g serving) plus some salt, if you like.
        To shorten the cooking time, add boiling water. Bring to a boil.</string>
    <string name="chapati">chapati is also known as Roti, Shabaati, Safati or Roshi
        in the Maldives. It is as unleavened flat bread which is a staple in
        Sri Lanka, India, Bangladesh and Nepal, usually made from Whole Whet Flour,
        though All Purpose Flour is normally used to make the Chapati.
        Chapati has many Varieties like Paneer Chapati where grated Paneer is
        added to the Chapati Dough. There is Radish or Mullandi Chapati where
        grated Radish and Turmeric Powder is added to the Chapati Dough, and
        also Vegetable Stuffed Chapati where Carrot, Potato, Fenugreek and Peas
        are mushed and  slightly sauteed into a Marsala gravy and then rolled
        into the Chapati.As you can see, there are so many ways that you can
        make this traditional Indian Flat Bread. Chapatis are a great meal because
        you can make them and reheat them the next day to have with Tea or a chosen
        Vegetable or Meat with it. The secret to making very Soft delicious
        Chapati is in the Dough, the kneading process is what really determines
        how soft your Chapati will become. Also I used hot water to knead the doug
        h and added Vegetable Oil before completing the kneading process.
        This makes the dough soft yet firm. So here is my very detailed steps to
        making the perfect and softest Chapati.</string>
    <string name="beans">fried beans are prepare by heating the oil in a
        large skillet over medium heat. Add the onion and cook until tender,
        about 3 minutes. Stir in the garlic and chili powder and cook for 1
        minute more. Stir in the beans and broth and cook until the beans are
        warmed through, about 5 minutes. Mash the beans coarsely with the
        back of a wooden spoon, adding more broth to moisten, if needed.
        Season with salt and pepper, to taste. Stir in the cilantro. Green Grams
        are annual legume crops grown for their seed. Grams could be green,
        black or yellow in colour. The green grams are the most commonly grown
        in Kenya. Grams are native crops of India. Often called green gram or golden
        , it is cultivated in several countries of Asia, Africa, and the Americas.
        The dried beans are prepared by cooking or milling. They are eaten whole
        or split. The seeds or the flour may be used in a variety of dishes like
        soups, porridge, snacks, bread, noodles and even ice cream. Green gram also
        produces great sprouts, which can be sold in health food shops or eaten at
        home. Crop residues of V. radiata are a useful fodder. Green gram is
        sometimes specifically grown for hay, green manure or as a cover crop.</string>
    <string name="stewedpotatoes">they are prepared by heating the oil in a
        skillet over medium heat, and saute the garlic and onion until tender.
        Stir in the tomato, and cook until heated through. Mix in potatoes
        and rutabaga. Season with oregano,salt, and pepper. Pour in the broth,
        and bring to a boil. Reduce heat to low, and continue cooking 15
        minutes, or until potatoes and rutabaga are tender. </string>
    <string name="githeri">Githeri, also called muthere or mutheri, is a Kenyan
        traditional meal of maize and legumes, mostly beans of any type mixed
        and boiled together. The maize and beans are mixed together in a sufuria
        or pot, water is then added and the mixture boiled until the food
        is cooked and ready to eat.</string>
    <string name="fruit">the common fruits in the mess are bananas and watermelon.
        Despite the popular belief that watermelon is just water
        and sugar, watermelon is actually a nutrient dense food. It provides high
        levels of vitamins, minerals, and antioxidants and just a small number
        of calories.Bananas are one of the most widely consumed fruits in the
        world for good reason. Eating them could help lower blood pressure and
        reduce the risks of cancer and asthma. </string>
    <string name="vegetables">the most common vegetables in the mess are
        sukumawiki(kales) and cabbage. sukumawiki is cooked by heating olive oil in
        a large saucepan over medium-high heat. Add the garlic and cook until soft,
        but not colored. Raise heat to high, add the stock and kale and toss to
        combine. Cover and cook for 5 minutes. Remove cover and continue to cook,
        stirring until all the liquid has evaporated. Season with salt and pepper
        to taste and add vinegar.cabbage is prepared by inserting a steamer basket
        inside a saucepan. Add enough water to the pan so the water level is just
        below the bottom of the basket.Bring water to boiling. Add cabbage wedges
        to steamer basket. Cover and steam for 10 to 12 minutes or until cabbage
        is crisp-tender. </string>
    <string name="beefstew">Beef stew is the benevolent king of all stews.
        Familiar yet never tiresome, chunks of tender beef and potatoes in rich
        brown gravy will always bring comfort and joy to our tables. Little things
        are what elevate a good stew to become a great one. Taking time to sear
        the beef is integral to flavor in both the meat and the gravy, as is
        letting it simmer low and slow until the beef is spoon-tender.
        Busy cooks might be tempted to purchase packages of so-called stew meat
        at the market, but it pays to follow this recipe and take a few minutes
        to cut up an economical chuck roast. Stew meat is a mixture of scraps
        left over when a butcher trims a range of cuts to go in the meat case,
        and these random pieces won’t cook the same way or finish at the same time
        . The uniformity of a well-marbled chuck roast yields consistent results
        and the best flavor. Originally, this recipe called for the stew to be
        cooked in a wok, which was trendy at the time. We prefer using a Dutch
        oven because it provides a large, flat surface to properly brown the meat.</string>
    <string name="friedbeef"> Fried Beef meat is the most tasty food to consume, and yet
        very expensive.But due to the urge to eat some, ill help you make 
        it better. At least solve some health complications caused by beef meat.
        Beef meat should not be roasted or pan fried. Trust me, it,s almost equal
        to eating it raw. Boiling, wet frying, oven cooking, grinding, etc are
        among the best methods of cooking beef</string>
    <string name="friedchicken">Fried chicken  is a dish consisting of chicken pieces
        usually from broiler chickens which have been floured or battered and then
        pan-fried, deep fried, or pressure fried. The breading adds a crisp coating
        or crust to the exterior of the chicken. What separates fried chicken from
        other fried forms of chicken is that generally the chicken is cut at the joints,
        and the bones and skin are left intact. Crisp well-seasoned skin, rendered
        of excess fat, is a hallmark of well made fried chicken. </string>
    <string name="stewedbeef">Beef sold for stew (that is, trimmed and cut into
        bite-size cubes) is generally chuck or round—tough cuts that become
        tender and flavorful when slowly simmered in liquid. Beef round cuts
        (bottom and eye) are generally leaner than chuck (shoulder, leg and butt)
        and very well-suited to stew.</string>
    <string name="pilau"> pilau is a dish, originating from the Indian subcontinent,
        in which rice is cooked in a seasoned broth. In some cases, the rice may
        attain its brown or golden color by first being sauteed lightly in oil
        before the addition of broth. Cooked onion, garlic cloves, sliced carrot,
        other vegetables, as well as a mix of spices, may be added. Depending on
        the local cuisine, it may additionally contain meat, fish, vegetables,
        pasta (orzo), or dried fruit.</string>
    <string name="salad">A salad is a dish consisting of a mixture of small pieces
        of food, usually vegetables. However, different varieties of salad may
        contain virtually any type of ready-to-eat food. Salads are typically
        served at room temperature or chilled.Garden salads use a base of leafy greens
        such as lettuce, arugula/rocket, kale or spinach; they are common enough
        that the word salad alone often refers specifically to garden salads</string>

</resources>
